{
"questions": [
  {
    "question": "Flask is a ____ framework?",
    "options": ["Frontend", "Backend", "Database", "Testing"],
    "answer": "Backend"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which language is Flask built with?",
   " options": ["Python", "JavaScript", "Java", "C#"],
    "answer": "Python"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which template engine does Flask commonly use?",
    "options": ["EJS", "Jinja2", "Pug", "Handlebars"],
    "answer": "Jinja2"
  },
  {
    "question": "Flask follows which type of architecture?",
    "options": ["MVC", "MVVM", "MVP", "None"],
    "answer": "MVC"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which command is used to run a Flask application?",
    "options": ["python app.py", "flask run", "npm start", "node server.js"],
    "answer": "flask run"
  },
  {
    "question": "What file is typically used to define routes in a Flask app?",
    "options": ["routes.py", "app.py", "index.html", "server.js"],
    "answer": "app.py"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which method is used to handle form submission in Flask?",
    "options": ["GET", "POST", "FETCH", "PUT"],
    "answer": "POST"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which decorator is used to define a route in Flask?",
    "options": ["@route", "@app.route", "@get", "@flask.route"],
    "answer": "@app.route"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do you render an HTML template in Flask?",
    "options": ["render_template()", "show_html()", "display_page()", "render_page()"],
    "answer": "render_template()"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which object is used to get form data in Flask?",
    "options": ["request", "form", "data", "input"],
    "answer": "request"
  }
  ]
}